Guide to the Whitman College Archives Walla Walla Vertical Files Collection approximately 1900-2005
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
Whitman College Archives Walla Walla Vertical Files Collection
approximately 1900-2005
Whitman College and Northwest Archives 345 Boyer Avenue Walla Walla, WA 99362 Archives@whitman.edu https://library.whitman.edu/archives/
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
WCA153
22.75 linear feet 14 filing cabinet drawers
The Whitman College Archives Walla Walla Vertical Files Collection contains subject files pertaining to the history of Walla Walla.
Collection is open for research.
The Whitman College and Northwest Archives has maintained a vertical file since at least the 1960s. From the beginning, the purpose of the vertical file was to arrange and store small files on a topic, often including memorabilia and ephemeral material, pertaining to Walla Walla. For the most part, the vertical file contains only printed items. Manuscript material and other unique items were, generally, not placed in the vertical file. Some of the materials in the vertical file include: newspaper clippings, press releases, programs, speeches, reprints, and obituaries. Since the early 2000s, material has not been regularly added to the collection, but staff do occassionaly add small additions.
The Whitman College Archives Walla Walla Vertical Files collection contains subject files organized alphabetically by topic. Materials within include fliers, brochures, posters, publications, newspaper clippings, informational packets, reports, and biographical information on events, buildings and topics related to Walla Walla.
Walla Walla (Wash.)--History
City and Town Life
Ephemera
- Agriculture: Agricultural Conservation Program, WW County, 1950, 1960, 26 page booklet
- Agriculture: Agricultural Conservation Program, WW County, 1951. 20 page document addressing county conservation program.
- Agriculture: Developments, technological advances
- Agriculture: herbs
- Agriculture: Machinery and equipment
- Agriculture: trees
- Agriculture: issues
- Agriculture: Chamber of Commerce Agricultural committee
- Agriculture: education
- Agriculture: publications
- Agriculture: maps, facts, and figures
- Agriculture: Dairy
- Agriculture: Agriculture Walla Walla County
- Agriculture: Seed Catalog collection for U.S., WW, and Milton-Freewater.
- Agriculture: Planting guides: gardening, 1883, 1943
- Agriculture: Walla Walla County agriculture conservation program
- Agriculture: Walla Walla County Agriculture Stabilization and Conservation Service (ASCS)
- Agriculture: Walla Walla Grain Growers, Inc. Restated By-Laws and Amended Articles of Incorporation, Pamphlet published January 1984
- Agriculture: Walla Walla Farmers Co-Op, Inc., Articles of Incorporation, May 9, 1955
- Agriculture: misc/general
- Agriculture: crops: alfalfa, hay and seed 1980
- Agriculture: crop: apple
- Agriculture: asparagus
- Agriculture: Asparagus
- Agriculture: crop reports
- Agriculture: farmer's market
- Agriculture: farmers strike
- Agriculture: foods
- Agriculture: fruit orchards, vineyards
- Agriculture: fruit and vegetables
- Agriculture: Gran (2 files)
- Agriculture: Wheat (2 files)
- Agriculture: walla walla "horse era"
- Agriculture: Horses, Horse clubs, '59ers, Posses (2 files)
- Agriculture: livestock
- Agriculture: Marygolds
- Agriculture: onions
- Agriculture: peas, beans, minor crops
- Agriculture: people: farmers, inspectors, awards given to
- Agriculture: Pesticides, pest control: DDT controversy
- Agriculture: poultry
- Agriculture: subsidies to farmers
- Agriculture: Walla Walla Gardener's Association
- Agriculture: winery
- Agriculture: labor camps
- Airport: aviation
- Airport: "flying news" publication 1929
- Airport: Program: World's Champion Air Show 1932 (Check the dates! This is most likely the one donated by Jerry Cundiff, Jr., 1991. )
- Airport: Sky Chief Airline Schedules. October 1, 1949 (Shows departure/arrival times for Walla Walla, fares, one way or round trip and destination)
- Airport: walla walla airport
- Airport: air base at the airport
- Antiques: General
- Archaeology: General
- Archaeology: Archaeology Society
- Architecture: Builders of Washington
- Architecture: Walla Walla architecture
- Architecture: sister city New South Wales
- Arts: Museums
- Arts: Porter Garnett, "A Pageant of May" script, performed in WW May 22, 23 1914, sponsored by Woman's Park Club
- Arts: Programs: WW Artists' Bureau
- Arts: Players Club of Walla Walla Program. Three One-Act plays WW High School Auditorium, December 3, 1926
- Arts: Program: Ted Shawn and His Male Dancers programs, clippings, info
- Arts: Woman's Park Club May Festival programs, librettos: music, organization. 1915, 1916, 1917
- Arts: Player's Club scrapbook 1920s, Walla Walla Theater
- Arts: Walla Walla Baroque. Flyers
- Arts: General (2 files)
- Arts: artists
- Arts: artists, art exhibits, art galleries
- Arts: arts
- Arts: art exhibits, etc.
- Arts: carpentry, woodworking, marquetry
- Arts: dance, ballet
- Arts: literature, peotry, storytelling
- Arts: misc/general
- Arts: music, concerts, musicians 1979
- Arts: Hampson, Thomas
- Arts: Walla Walla Foundry
- Arts: music in Walla Walla
- Arts: the Shepherd's Staff
- Arts: Walla Walla Valley Youth Chorous
- Arts: painting, etching, engravings, prints, photography
- Arts: Summer Dance Lab
- Arts: sculpture, pottery
- Arts: theatres - misc/general
- Arts: Columbine players - summer theatre
- Arts: Theatres - Walla Walla Little Theatre
- Arts: Little Theatre
- Arts: Walla Walla Jazz Society
- Arts: Theatre (2 files)
- Arts: Walla Walla Chamber Music Festival
- Arts: Drama materials
- Arts: Blanchet, F. N.
- Businesses/Buildings: Booklet: "Book of Toasts," compiled by R.H. Keene, compliments of The Fountain Saloon, A. Schwarz, proprietor, Walla Walla (1 booklet, with ads from WW businesses)
- Businesses/Buildings: Stine House itemized 1890 inventory (copy)
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Canning Inst.
- Businesses/Buildings: Photograph: Walla Walla Telephone Bldg.
- Businesses/Buildings: Ritz Nursery 30th Annual Catalogue
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Creamery and Cheese Factory monthly statement, June 1903
- Businesses/Buildings: Arbini Farms
- Businesses/Buildings: Army Corps of Engineers
- Businesses/Buildings: misc/general
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Production Credit Association. 20th Anniversary Report 1953 (20th Anniversary Report)
- Businesses/Buildings: businesses - general (3 folders)
- Businesses/Buildings: Businesses - Billheads 1930's
- Businesses/Buildings: businesses 1978
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla businesses
- Businesses/Buildings: AAA
- Businesses/Buildings: Abajian
- Businesses/Buildings: Audubon Society
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla businesses 1979
- Businesses/Buildings: Backstage Bistro
- Businesses/Buildings: Bee Hive
- Businesses/Buildings: Beehive salon
- Businesses/Buildings: Building Permits
- Businesses/Buildings: Blue Mt. Mall
- Businesses/Buildings: Bon Ton Restaurant
- Businesses/Buildings: Bon Marche
- Businesses/Buildings: Book Nook Drugs
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Brewing Co. Certificate
- Businesses/Buildings: Britt's Store
- Businesses/Buildings: Ben Greco and Sons Tailors
- Businesses/Buildings: Ben Hunt manufacturing co.
- Businesses/Buildings: Barrett Building
- Businesses/Buildings: Best Western Suites Inn
- Businesses/Buildings: Bennington Apartment (Mulkey)
- Businesses/Buildings: Big 5 Sporting Goods
- Businesses/Buildings: Blue Mt. Industry
- Businesses/Buildings: Boise Cascade
- Businesses/Buildings: Bookery
- Businesses/Buildings: book store
- Businesses/Buildings: Bowers' Gourmets
- Businesses/Buildings: Breier Building
- Businesses/Buildings: Burnett, Malen School of Music
- Businesses/Buildings: Capitol Theatre
- Businesses/Buildings: Canneries
- Businesses/Buildings: Cinderella Shoe Shine Stand
- Businesses/Buildings: Closing of Businesses
- Businesses/Buildings: Coffey Communications
- Businesses/Buildings: Copelaud
- Businesses/Buildings: Country Club
- Businesses/Buildings: Croft's Flowers
- Businesses/Buildings: Davis Kaser
- Businesses/Buildings: Vanderahe, William (creamery and cold storage)
- Businesses/Buildings: Dements Best Flour
- Businesses/Buildings: DeMoss store
- Businesses/Buildings: Denny building
- Businesses/Buildings: department stores
- Businesses/Buildings: the deopt
- Businesses/Buildings: destruction of buildings
- Businesses/Buildings: DeWitt Ambulance Service
- Businesses/Buildings: Drumheller Co.
- Businesses/Buildings: Duff's Dairy Store
- Businesses/Buildings: Eastwind Martial Arts Association
- Businesses/Buildings: Economy Drug Store
- Businesses/Buildings: Edgewater Pavilion
- Businesses/Buildings: Elks
- Businesses/Buildings: Ernst Home Center
- Businesses/Buildings: Exchange Building
- Businesses/Buildings: Falkenbergs
- Businesses/Buildings: Farmer's general Trading co
- Businesses/Buildings: Fire Station
- Businesses/Buildings: Flower Mill
- Businesses/Buildings: Frontier Machinery
- Businesses/Buildings: full circle
- Businesses/Buildings: foundation for the preservation of the Governor's Mansion
- Businesses/Buildings: Georgia Pacific corp
- Businesses/Buildings: goodwill industries
- Businesses/Buildings: Grand central market
- Businesses/Buildings: grand hotel
- Businesses/Buildings: grocery stores
- Businesses/Buildings: Green and Jackson (formerly Stewart Holmes Drug Store)
- Businesses/Buildings: Harold Electric
- Businesses/Buildings: Harris
- Businesses/Buildings: Herman's sporting goods
- Businesses/Buildings: Gus Lindberg Shoe Repair
- Businesses/Buildings: Historic Preservation of Buildings
- Businesses/Buildings: historic buildings
- Businesses/Buildings: Holt
- Businesses/Buildings: Homestead
- Businesses/Buildings: Business invoices and letter head
- Businesses/Buildings: Holly's Flowers
- Businesses/Buildings: Jacobi's Jefferis Agency inc
- Businesses/Buildings: Jensen Building (the bonmarche)
- Businesses/Buildings: G. W. Jones' grocery store
- Businesses/Buildings: jones scott co
- Businesses/Buildings: k-mart
- Businesses/Buildings: key technology
- Businesses/Buildings: keylor grand theatre (2 folders)
- Businesses/Buildings: Kirkman House
- Businesses/Buildings: Lee Gee's Brick
- Businesses/Buildings: Kirkwood Historic Ranch
- Businesses/Buildings: legal, governmental
- Businesses/Buildings: Leonetti's Resaurant
- Businesses/Buildings: La Casita
- Businesses/Buildings: Liberty Theatre
- Businesses/Buildings: Little Ceasar's Pizza
- Businesses/Buildings: logging industry
- Businesses/Buildings: logos of Walla Walla
- Businesses/Buildings: Loney's Harvest food
- Businesses/Buildings: Louvre saloon
- Businesses/Buildings: Ludwigs jewelry
- Businesses/Buildings: Marcus Whitman Hotel
- Businesses/Buildings: Whitman Motor Inn
- Businesses/Buildings: McBride building
- Businesses/Buildings: Main Street Cycles
- Businesses/Buildings: Martin Archery
- Businesses/Buildings: Martin's Jewelers
- Businesses/Buildings: McFeely Hotel
- Businesses/Buildings: Melody Muffler
- Businesses/Buildings: The Midway
- Businesses/Buildings: Model grocery
- Businesses/Buildings: Montgomery Word co
- Businesses/Buildings: Niemi, Hollaud and scott
- Businesses/Buildings: Monroe Auto sales
- Businesses/Buildings: Northwest Library Bindery
- Businesses/Buildings: Odd Fellows
- Businesses/Buildings: Oasis
- Businesses/Buildings: Onion World
- Businesses/Buildings: P. P. L. co
- Businesses/Buildings: Paine Building
- Businesses/Buildings: Park Plaza
- Businesses/Buildings: Pantorium Cleaners
- Businesses/Buildings: Pataha's Flour mill
- Businesses/Buildings: Pay n' Pack
- Businesses/Buildings: Pastime café
- Businesses/Buildings: Paula Ray Gallery
- Businesses/Buildings: Piggly Wiggly food store
- Businesses/Buildings: Pioneer Brewing co
- Businesses/Buildings: Pioneer Title co
- Businesses/Buildings: Plaza Cinemas
- Businesses/Buildings: Pony Soldier
- Businesses/Buildings: Prescott Home
- Businesses/Buildings: Private Utilities
- Businesses/Buildings: Recycling (3 files)
- Businesses/Buildings: Red Apple
- Businesses/Buildings: Red Horse Ranch
- Businesses/Buildings: Remodeled milling co
- Businesses/Buildings: Rees Hotel
- Businesses/Buildings: Rees Winans building
- Businesses/Buildings: Revenue office
- Businesses/Buildings: Restaurants, eating establishments
- Businesses/Buildings: Reynold's Day
- Businesses/Buildings: Roxy Theatre
- Businesses/Buildings: Stahl Opera House
- Businesses/Buildings: Safeway
- Businesses/Buildings: St. Paul Apartments
- Businesses/Buildings: Sea Gallery
- Businesses/Buildings: 72 messenger service
- Businesses/Buildings: Salvation Army
- Businesses/Buildings: Schwabacher Bros.
- Businesses/Buildings: Schwartz Building
- Businesses/Buildings: Sears
- Businesses/Buildings: Sporleders
- Businesses/Buildings: State Hotel
- Businesses/Buildings: Stencil Hotel
- Businesses/Buildings: Stine House Hotel
- Businesses/Buildings: Straight Building
- Businesses/Buildings: Star Laundry
- Businesses/Buildings: Shady Lawn
- Businesses/Buildings: St. Vincent dePaul Society
- Businesses/Buildings: Strauser Manufacturing inc
- Businesses/Buildings: Sunshine Chevrolet-Cadillac
- Businesses/Buildings: Super 1 foods
- Businesses/Buildings: Super 8 motel
- Businesses/Buildings: Telephone Co building site
- Businesses/Buildings: tino's café
- Businesses/Buildings: Tomlinson
- Businesses/Buildings: Treasure shop
- Businesses/Buildings: Troy School
- Businesses/Buildings: The Turf
- Businesses/Buildings: Twin Peaks Error Coin Museum
- Businesses/Buildings: U.S. West
- Businesses/Buildings: U - Haul
- Businesses/Buildings: Van Pelleu Lumber Co
- Businesses/Buildings: Uptown music
- Businesses/Buildings: U.S. Army Corps of Engineers
- Businesses/Buildings: Waitsburg Mill
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Brewing Co
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Country Club
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Foundry
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Iron Works
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Motor Supply inc
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Produce Co
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Steam Laundry
- Businesses/Buildings: Walmart
- Businesses/Buildings: Watermill foods
- Businesses/Buildings: Whitehouse Crawford
- Businesses/Buildings: Canneries
- Businesses/Buildings: Wine
- Businesses/Buildings: Woolworth, F.W. Company flyer for annual Mid-Summer clearance sale, 1913
- Businesses/Buildings: Yocum-Peterson Inc.bills, etc. 1929-1930
- Businesses/Buildings: Dahlen Brothers Auto Dealership, letter about
- Businesses/Buildings: Empire Business College copy of large business card, WT
- Businesses/Buildings: Ringhoffer Brothers letterhead
- Businesses/Buildings: Philip Ritz business card, Washington Territory
- Businesses/Buildings: Sherwood and Roberts Records. 1979 pamphlet
- Businesses/Buildings: The Song Shop listing of music-Century's Edition
- Businesses/Buildings: Stewart's French Dry Cleaners
- Businesses/Buildings: Tracy and Company Express bill, 1861
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Electro Plating Works
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Gum Company correspondence with Knoxville, TN
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Meat and Cold Storage Company Records. pamphlet
- Businesses/Buildings: Walla Walla Realty Association Association Records, 1909-1917. articles of incorporation, minutes
- Businesses/Buildings: Weber's, Frank Sons Tannery copy of photo: business, image
- Businesses/Buildings: W.C. Whitney, business card WW Home Nurseries: business
- Businesses/Buildings: Malcolm McLean Grocery Company Records. 1908-1942 minute book; 1913 grocery price list; 2 folders
- Businesses/Buildings: Grayson Maxwell closing out Jensen Art Department 1927
- Businesses/Buildings: Pacific Power and Light gas meter rate 1911
- Businesses/Buildings: Inland Empire Produce Company 1902 contract to erect "packing house and stables"
- Businesses/Buildings: Hockett Drug Co
- Businesses/Buildings: Grand Hotel banquet program, Business and Professional Women's clubs 1931
- Businesses/Buildings: Copeland Building open house announcement
- Businesses/Buildings: The Delta tobacco shop records, F.E. Stanfield proprietor
- Businesses/Buildings: Book Nook 1915 article of agreement
- Businesses/Buildings: Hotel Dacres Records. misc. papers
- Celebrations and Events: St. Louis Hotel
- Celebrations and Events: Foster Orchard Sprinkles Letterhead
- Celebrations and Events: Fourth of July program 1895 (2 folders)
- Celebrations and Events: Freedom Train programs, information 1948
- Celebrations and Events: Carneigie Arts Center (4 folders)
- Celebrations and Events: misc/general
- Celebrations and Events: Bicentennial clippings and Fourth of July celebration map of Pioneer Park
- Celebrations and Events: celebrations 1936
- Celebrations and Events: Centennial observance of Stevens Treaty Council 1955
- Census: Walla Walla Centennial 1959
- Census: Centennial 1989
- Census: Walla Walla census
- Census: Census Bureau
- Chamber of Commerce: Community Chest suggested articles of association
- City Council: Parker Barrett report, president of WW Chamber of Commerce 1940
- City Council: Softball Tournament Program of August 23-26, 1951 contains facts ( 1928-1951) about WW softball: Kitten Ball, Twilight League, and Rover Boys.
- City Council: City Government 1862-1892
- City Council: city-misc.
- City Council: Education
- City Council: misc/general
- City Council: city 1979
- City Council: city 1978
- City Council: city of Walla Walla
- City Council: Walla Walla
- City Council: City Attorney
- City Council: Area report
- City Council: City of Walla Walla at your service
- City Council: Bicentennial committee (3 folders)
- City Council: City Board of Adjustment (7 folders)
- City Council: Board of Commissioners
- City Council: Budget cuts
- City Council: Civil Service Commission (2 folders)
- City Council: Community Congress
- City Council: City Council 1980
- City Council: City Council (7 folders)
- City Council: City Council 1981
- City Council: City - County Consolidation
- City Council: Department of Communittee Development
- City Council: Court district
- City Council: Downtown Development
- City Council: City Engineers
- City Council: City Employees
- City Council: City Expenses and Funds (2 folders)
- City Council: Finance Director (2 folders)
- City Council: Finances 1978-1979
- City Council: Finances 1980-1981
- City Council: City Government
- City Council: City Hall
- City Council: Department of Human Resources
- City Council: Juvenile Department
- City Council: City Manager
- City Council: City Planning
- City Council: Planning Commission (2 folders)
- City Council: Property Tax
- City Council: City Public Works Department
- City Council: City Recreation Program
- City Council: Sanitation Department
- City Council: City Sign Code
- City Council: Utilities (3 folders)
- City Council: Utilities 1978-1979
- City Council: Utilities 1980
- City Council: Utilities 1981
- City Council: Utilities 1983
- City Council: Water Supply
- City Jail: Hydro power hydroelectric projects
- City Jail: Walla Walla, Illinois
- Climate: Climate
- Climate: Autumn
- Climate: Fog, wind, dust storms, smog
- Climate: rain, tornadoes, floods
- Climate: Summer
- Climate: Winter
- Climate: Weather 1977
- Climate: Weather 1978
- Climate: Weather (4 folders)
- Climate: Weather 1979
- Climate: Weather 1996
- Climate: Climate 1996
- Climate: Climate 1997
- Clubs: Blue Mountain Riders of Walla Walla. Purpose and By-Laws. Walla Walla women's riding club.
- Clubs: Walla Walla 10 step club
- Clubs: Commercial Club
- Clubs: Walla Walla Commercial Club
- Clubs: Walla Walla Yacht Club Inc. Records (3 folders)
- Clubs: Exchange Club Sam Snead golfing exhibition program, 1980
- Clubs: Walla Walla Wings Airshow club
- Clubs: WW Dancing Club letter, 1922
- Clubs: Evergreen Dancing Club reply card undated, Walla Walla
- Clubs: Walla Walla Knife and Fork Club lRecords. list of members, Charter night program 1952-1953; program 1963-1964 (2 folders)
- Clubs: City Club (photographs) c.1959
- Conventions: Telephone
- Conventions: TV and Radio
- Conventions:
- Conventions: Conventions at Walla Walla
- Councils: misc/general
- Councils: Citizens' Advisory Committee
- Councils: Citizen's Committee
- Councils: Community Congress
- Councils: Communittee Service Council
- Councils: Literacy Council
- Councils: Valley Cultural Awareness Committee
- County of Columbia: Blue Wood
- County of Columbia: Columbia Basin Irrigation Project
- County of Columbia: Christos Press Dayton
- County of Columbia: Columbia County (8 folders)
- County of Columbia: American Cancer Society
- County of Columbia: Churches and religion
- County of Columbia: Columbia County Commissioners (8 folders)
- County of Columbia: Crime: Assault, Kidnapping, missing persons
- County of Columbia: Expenses and funds
- County of Columbia: Columbia County Fair (3 folders)
- County of Columbia: Finances
- County of Columbia: Mosquito Control District
- County of Columbia: Columbia River
- County of Columbia: Columbia School District (4 folders)
- County of Columbia: Streets and Roads (2 folders)
- County of Columbia: Superior Court 1980
- County of Columbia: crops: grain, vegetables
- County of Columbia: Dayton (15 folders)
- County of Columbia: Robinson / Stahl Saddle Shop
- County of Columbia: Dayton businesses
- County of Columbia: Dayton Chamber of Commerce
- County of Columbia: Dayton City Council (5 folders)
- County of Columbia: Dayton Days
- County of Columbia: Dayton Depot Corp
- County of Columbia: Dayton Schools (5 folders)
- County of Columbia: Fort Taylor
- County of Columbia: Lyons Ferry
- County of Columbia: Ports of Columbia, Umatilla
- County of Columbia: Rivers
- County of Columbia: Dayton Police Dept.
- County of Columbia: Water, waterways
- County of Columbia: Starbuck (8 folders)
- County of Garfield: Tucannon
- County of Garfield: Waitsburg
- County of Garfield:
- County of Garfield: Houser Flour Mill
- County of Garfield: Garfield County
- County of Garfield: Garfield Country Commissioners
- County of Garfield: Telegraph
- County of Garfield: Pataha
- County of Garfield: Pomeroy Town (5 folders)
- County of Garfield: Meteorite
- County of Garfield: Garfield County
- County of Garfield: History of Garfield County book
- County of Umatilla: Adams (2 folders)
- County of Umatilla: Agriculture
- County of Umatilla: Town of Athena (13 folders): school district, city council
- County of Umatilla: churches
- County of Umatilla: Pendleton Academy
- County of Umatilla: Franzien Farmstead
- County of Umatilla: Ferndale (6 folders): state line and aster show
- County of Umatilla: State Line from Econimics Club Ferndale
- County of Umatilla: Fruitvale
- County of Umatilla: Heppner
- County of Umatilla: Hot Lake Oregon
- County of Umatilla: Meoeham
- County of Umatilla: Milton - Freewater (24 folders): schools, planning commission, agriculture
- County of Umatilla: American Red Cross and Cancer Society
- County of Umatilla: Crime: Assault, Kidnapping, missing persons
- County of Umatilla: watershed
- County of Umatilla: Valley Herald
- County of Umatilla: Pendleton (6 folders)
- County of Umatilla: Stanfield
- County of Umatilla: Tomastslikt Cultural Institute
- County of Umatilla: Tum-A-Lum Community Education Program (4 folders)
- County of Umatilla: Tollgate Oregon
- County of Umatilla: Umapine Oregon (5 folders)
- County of Umatilla: Umatilla County (20 folders): courts, commissioners, extension agents, sheriff's department, fire protection district
- County of Umatilla: Umatilla Canning Co
- County of Umatilla: Thomas Ruckel Road
- County of Umatilla: Umatilla Gas Deopt
- County of Umatilla: Umatilla Indian Reservation
- County of Umatilla: Umatilla Indians
- County of Umatilla: Umatilla River
- County of Umatilla: Umatilla National Forest
- County of Umatilla: Tollgate Area 1981
- County of Umatilla: Weston (5 folders)